<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-01-14T08:46:25+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Eugene Choy Wen Jia</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Happy Toilet Social Analytics</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/social/analytics/2019/08/01/HappyToilet.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Happy Toilet Social Analytics" /><published>2019-08-01T18:44:42+08:00</published><updated>2019-08-01T18:44:42+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/social/analytics/2019/08/01/HappyToilet</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/social/analytics/2019/08/01/HappyToilet.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I embarked on this project as part of a module called Social Analytics and Applications. We were required to look for a client who may have a social business problem that we can look into. We decided to work with Restroom Association to identify social trends and insights from Social Media with regards to public toilet in Singapore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;data-analysis&quot;&gt;Data Analysis&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;data-collection&quot;&gt;Data Collection&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team collected data from sources such as Reddit, Twitter, Instagram and TripAdvisor using Web Scrapping techniques and various APIS available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;data-cleaning&quot;&gt;Data Cleaning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the data were collected from various Social Media source, there was a need to clean the data as there were some post that were captured which were not toilet related. We did some filtering by looking for keywords in the various post such as “urinal,cubicle,toilet,dirty,flush,poop,shit”. Post without any of the relevant toilet keywords were ommitted for further analysis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;insights-gathered&quot;&gt;Insights Gathered&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;visualization&quot;&gt;Visualization&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wordmap&quot;&gt;WordMap&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;topics-modelled&quot;&gt;Topics Modelled&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;flask-web-app&quot;&gt;Flask Web App&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;recommendations&quot;&gt;Recommendations&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;social-media-campaign&quot;&gt;Social Media Campaign&lt;/h2&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction I embarked on this project as part of a module called Social Analytics and Applications. We were required to look for a client who may have a social business problem that we can look into. We decided to work with Restroom Association to identify social trends and insights from Social Media with regards to public toilet in Singapore.</summary></entry></feed>